(忆往昔)
离开你我该怎么办啊
What would I do without you?
不要啊
No
有东西把他转变成了怪物
Something turned him into a monster.
我们面对的是什么  你知道吗
What we are dealing with, you know?
恶魔病毒的幸存者
Croatoan survivals
全都染上瘟疫了
with plague and pestilence
天知道这瘟疫会传多远
who knows how far this thing can spread?
你是克劳力  对吧
It's "Crowley," right?
为什么
Why...
你这么想路西法死呢
exactly would you want the devil dead?
为了生存
Survival.
如果路西法想要
If Lucifer manages
灭了你们人类
to exterminate humankind
那我们自然命不久矣了
We're next.
那个关路西法的牢笼
The cage you sprung lucifer from
你们可以再把他扔回去
you can shove his ass back in.
想要打开牢笼
The key to the cage?
需要四个戒指
Four rings.
天启四骑士手上的
From the horsemen.
我们拿到了战争的
We got war's.
还拿到了饥荒的
We nicked famine's.
我们有2个戒指了  只要拿到瘟疫和死亡的
That's two rings down. Collect all four.
我们就凑齐4枚戒指了
Just need pestilence and death.
就这样吗
Oh, is that all?
(如今)
我只是很高兴我们能为患者提供药物了
I'm just glad we got something to offer people.
真抱歉
Well, I'm sorry.
不过那全是废话  只是为了利益罢了
It's a load of crap -- pure profit-driven crap.
猪流感  是种流行病
Well, swine flu -- it's an epidemic.
如果尼维亚斯真那么在乎这场流行病的话
Yeah, well, if Niveus was really worried about the epidemic,
他们就该免费提供疫苗
they'd be giving the vaccine out for free.
弄个新配方算怎么回事
This supposed new formula?
他们说这个会更快见效
Well, they say it's faster-acting.
也许是吧  但干嘛这周就进行人体试验
Maybe it is, but human trials this week?
是啊  确实快了点儿
Yeah, it does seem a little rushed.
就快了"点儿"吗
A little rushed?
你有见到过新疫苗吗
Have you even seen the new vaccine?
-没  - 我也没
- No. - Yeah. Neither have I.
我见过了
I have.
你谁啊
Who the hell are you?
我要做个实验
I'm running an experiment.
搞什么鬼啊
What the hell?!
别紧张嘛  你也是实验的一部分
Relax. You're part of it, too.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
嘿  把门打开
Hi, open this door.
放开我  上帝啊  不要啊  放开
Aah! Aah! Get off of me! God, no! Get off! Aah!
哇哦  看起来起作用了
Well, looks like it works.
[邪恶力量 第5季第20集]
瞧瞧  我看起来像流行音乐之王
Check it out -- I look like the king of pop.
话题不和谐吗
Too soon?
看来不太和谐
Too soon.
别误会  我很高兴疾病防治中心的人来这儿
Don't get me wrong -- I'm glad the CDC is here,
但我们最需要的还是疫苗
but what we really need is vaccine.
你说得没错
You got that right.
先跟我说说
Well, tell me,
你有发现什么异常情况吗
have you noticed anything unusual about the strain --
有没有行为变化的迹象
Any signs of behavioral change,
比如侵袭什么的
like aggression, maybe?
什么意思
Excuse me?
流感患者有没有出现一些
Have the flu victims shown any signs of, uh,
杀人倾向
homicidal tendencies?
种种迹象表明  我们这里的
Symptomatically speaking, we're looking at
猪流感疫情相对来说并不严重
a relatively mild case of swine flu here.
顶多就是一周都病怏怏的不能上班
Probably add up to a miserable week off of work,
仅此而已
And that's about it.
也就是没任何异常咯
So nothing unusual.
一天半以前还没有任何病患
Day and a half ago, we didn't have a single case.
而现在却已经超过70例
Now we're looking at over 70 --
这传染速度也过于快了
The infectious equivalent of a briefcase bomb.
没错  我就觉得这点不太正常
So, yeah, I might call that a little unusual.
一天半
Day and a half?
同一时间  那些雕像也开始流泪了
That's the same time those statues started crying.
是的
Yep.
抱歉  什么来着
I'm sorry. What was that?
什么什么
What was what?
你刚是不是说一堆雕像开始流泪了
Did you just say a bunch of statues started crying?
什么  没有没有  谁会...
What? Why, no. No. W-who would --
谁会说那些啊  疯子吧
Who would say that, huh? Crazy people.
没错
Exactly.
没错  我们可正常了
Yeah, which we are not.
没错
No.
那就  给我们拨些疫苗吧
Just... get us some vaccine.
让我猜猜先  又一堆热气腾腾的猪流感患者
Let me guess -- another steamin'-hot pile of swine flu.
没错
Yep.
根本讲不通  鲍比
Doesn't make any sense, Bobby.
瘟疫一定来过这儿  我敢肯定
Pestilence touched down here. I'm sure of it.
但他为什么下手这么温柔  猪流感而已
But why is he dealing them soft serve like swine flu.
他不是有恶魔病毒在手吗
When he's got the croatoan virus up his sleeve?
我  我猜不透
I-I-I don't get it.
不管这狗娘养的心里打什么鬼主意
Doesn't matter what the sick son of a bitch is doing.
重要的是这是他袭击第四座城了
What matters is this is the fourth town he's hit --
就我们所知的而已  我们还连他影都没追到
That we know of -- and we're still eating his dust.
你们一点线索都没查到吗
Did you get anything?
我们真没一点可能推测到他下一个目标吗
We got even a snowball at probable next target?
我们还没找到规律
Uh, no pattern we can see.
好吧
Okay.
等一会
Hold on.
据我了解  他还是在继续向东走
Well, far as I can tell, he's still heading east,
那么  向东开吧
so... Head east, I guess.
-向东  - 向东
- East? - East?
鲍比  我们现在在内华达州西部
Bobby, we're in west Nevada.
东边也微远了点儿
East is practically all there is.
那么  你最好还是调头吧
Yeah, well, you better get to drivin'.
老实说
Say...
我倒是有个点子
I've got an idea.
得手了吗
Did you get him?
他消失了
He's gone.
想抽支烟谈谈心吗
Fancy a fag and a chat?
别那么急躁嘛  咱们应该先谈谈
You're upset. We should discuss it.
虽然地方不太对  但
Not here, but --
你想聊聊
You want to talk?
在你对我们做了那些好事儿之后
After what you did to us?
我对你们做什么了啊
After what I -- what I did to you?!
科尔特可是我给你们的
I gave you the colt!
没错  而你也知道它对路西法根本没用
Yeah, and you knew it wouldn't work against the devil!
-我压根就不知道  - 你骗了我们
- I never! - You set us up.
那场自杀式的袭击中我们失去了挚友
We lost people on that suicide run --
他们都是好人
Good people!
带谁去袭击是你们自己决定的  少赖我
Who you take on the ride is your own business!
听着  情况仍旧没变
Look, everything is still the same.
我们仍旧是一条战线上的
W-we're all still in this together.
当然了
Sure we are.
拜托把你家这只狗狗叫走
Call your dog off -- please.
给个理由先
Give me one good reason.
我能帮你们抓住瘟疫
I can give you pestilence.
你对瘟疫了解多少
What do you know about pestilence?
我知道怎么找到他
I know how to get him.
这应该正是你们想要的吧
That's got your interest, doesn't it?
-你不会真相信他了吧  - 萨姆
- Are you actually listening to this? - Sam --
-你脑子进水了吧  - 安静会  萨姆
- Are you friggin' nuts?! - Shut up for a second, sam!
你俩都给我闭嘴
Shut up, the both of you!
听着  我发誓
Look...I swear...
我本以为科尔特能杀死他的
I thought the colt would work.
那是无心之失
It's an honest mistake.
吃一堑  长一智
It's all part of the learning process.
但一切都没变  我仍想让路西法去死
But nothing's changed. I still want the devil dead.
话说回来  还是有点改变的
Well... One thing's changed.
现在路西法知道我想让他去死了
Now the devil knows that I want him dead.
于是我就成了
Which, by the way,
所有孩子里面麻烦最大的一个
makes me the most buggered son in all of creation.
少来了  关我们什么事
Holy crap. We don't care.
他们烧了我的房子
They burnt down my house!
还吃了我的裁缝
They ate my tailor!
两个月来  我都苟且偷生
Two months under a rock,
像是他妈的火蜥蜴
like a bloody salamander!
地上地下的恶魔们都在找我
Every demon on hell and earth's got his eyes out for me!
不过  我出现了
And yet... here I am...
在这个我最不该出现的地方
Last place I should be --
在这条路上  和温彻斯特兄弟说话
In the road, talking to Sam and Dean Winchester,
还是在见鬼的聚光灯下
under a friggin' spotlight!
跟我走吧  拜托了
So come with me. Please.
你们到底要不要天启四骑士的戒指了
Do you want the horsemen rings or not?
是  我都知道了
Yes, I know all about that.
可以走了吗
Shall we?
就是这了
Here we are --
我的逃命生活
My life on the lam.
虎落平阳啊
How the mighty have fallen.
单窗格玻璃
Single-pane glass,
连壁炉都要省着用
used contraception in the fireplace.
光是那些水渍
The water damage alone --
我真为你心痛
My heart's bleeding for you.
现在说说你怎么知道戒指的事的
Now, how do you know about the rings?
好吧
Well, now...
我一直密切关注着你们
I've been keeping a close eye on you lot.
我们有魔法袋  恶魔找不到我们的
We got hex bags. We're hidden from demons.
除了我
All but one.
你们闯入我家的那晚
That night you broke into my house,
就是我们初次见面那回
our first date,
我的侍从在你们车里藏了追踪装置
my valet hid a tracking device in your car --
一个魔法硬币
a magical coin
它能轻易敌过你们那小骨头魔法袋
that easily trumps your little bags o' bones.
也能让我听到你们的声音
It allows me to hear things, too --
然后  我被我听到的内容震惊了
and, my, the things I've heard.
你们想把路西法关回牢笼
So you want to cram the devil back in the box?
狡猾的计划
Cunning scheme.
带我一个
I want in.
你说能帮我们找到瘟疫
You said you could get us pestilence.
是这样的
Well, now...
我不知道瘟疫他本尊
I don't know where pestilence is...
在哪里
Per se.
但我知道哪个恶魔能告诉我们
But I do know the demon who does.
你们可以称他为天启四骑士的马童
He's what you might call the horsemen's stable boy.
他为他们安排行程以及日常所需
He handles their itineraries, their personal needs.
相信我  他就是你们要找的那位
He's who you want -- believe me.
他能告诉我们小喷嚏的方位
He'll tell us where sneezy's at.
我们怎么才能让他开口呢
Well, how do we get him to spill?
拔下他的脚趾甲吗
Rip out his toenails?
不用
No.
他那种等级的疯子可不吃那一套
Nuts at his pay grade don't crack.
我们把他带到这里  然后我来出售他
We bring him here, then I sell him.
出售他
Sell him?
拜托  我都向圣徒出售了几个世纪的罪恶了
Please. I've sold sin to saints for centuries.
难道我还搞不定区区一个小恶魔
Think I can't close one little demon?
好吧  那这个小恶魔在哪呢
All right, so where's this demon of yours?
(尼维亚斯)
我不想听到"还要几周"
I don't want to hear "Weeks."
我想听到"只需几天"
I want to hear "Days."
但是这个实验还在测试中
But the lab isn't even finished testing yet.
实验的事用不着你操心
You let me worry about the lab.
但是  先生  您要求的分布范围
But, sir, you're asking for distribution
实在是规模空前
on an unprecedented scale.
当然  我们有一场前所未有的突发事件
Well, we have an unprecedented outbreak.
我们国家正受到猪流感的威胁
The nation...is terrified of swine flu.
他们想要我们的疫苗  需要我们的疫苗
They want our vaccine. They need our vaccine.
这被称为"急需品"  同志们
It's called "Demand," People.
现在就开始供应
Now, supply!
我们已经尽全力了
We're doing our best.
你已经尽全力了
Oh, you're doing your best?
你真的尽全力了吗
You're doing your best?
那就比全力再多尽一份力
Well, then do the best of somebody better!
您找我吗
You wanted to see me?
米切尔  是的  进来
Mitchell, yes. Come on in.
听着  布雷迪先生  我知道这很重要
Look, Mr. Brady, I know how important this is,
对于之前的态度  我很抱歉
and I-I'm sorry if I sounded --
不用道歉
No apologies.
小米  我需要你这样的人才
Mitch, I need people like you.
真的吗
Really?
确实
Really.
事实上  在通讯部有个职位
In fact, there is a position in communications
我觉得非常适合你
that I think you would be perfect for.
听起来很棒
Sounds great.
的确  你怎么看
Is great. So what do you say?
你准备好加入
You ready to enter
竞争残酷的高层管理了吗
the cutthroat world of upper management?
太棒了
Awesome.
好极了
麻烦你  别弄脏我的鞋
Ooh. Watch the shoes, please.
迟些再叫其他人来  谢谢
Get the rest later. Thanks.
[咒语]
阁下  好消息
Sir, great news.
疫苗的试验结果
The vaccine trials -- the results have been...
绝对足够荒唐
...really quite grotesque.
我想你会高兴的
I think you'll be pleased.
要多久
How soon?
鉴于如此大规模的分布
Distribution on this scale --
我们需要更多人手
I mean, we do need some humans.
我们没法对每个人都附身
We can't possess them all.
想起那些所谓高层我就生气  我
And don't even get me started on the teamsters. I --
我知道  我会尽全力的
I know. I'm doing my best.
是的  阁下
Yes, sir.
比全力再多尽一份力
The best of someone better.
当然  我会的
I will. Of course.
我们为什么要听他的  迪恩
Why are we even listening to him, Dean?
这太疯狂了
This is totally insane.
我同意
I don't disagree.
我们是个相亲相爱的家庭吧  好极了
One big happy family, are we, then? Fantastic.
你准备好出发了吗
You ready to go?
是的  准备好了
Yes. Yes. I am.
萨姆  你就乖乖看家吧
Sam, keep the home fires burning.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
萨姆不和我们一起去
Sam's not coming.
为什么
And why the hell not?
因为我不喜欢你
Because I don't like you...
不信任你
I don't trust you...
还有  噢  对了
And -- oh, yes --
你一直都想杀死我
You keep trying to kill me.
没门儿  我一定要去
There's no damn way. This isn't gonna happen!
我并没有问你  因为你并没有被邀请
I'm not asking you, am I? 'cause you're not invited.
我是在问你  怎样
I'm asking you. What's it gonna be?
先生们
Gentlemen...
好好珍惜你们最后的日子吧
Enjoy your last few sunsets.
等等
Wait.
我去
I'll go.
我能说什么  我相信他
What can I say? I believe the guy.
然后迪恩和克劳力两个人
And then Dean just walks...
一起走了
...right out the door with Crowley.
萨姆  我对恶魔没有爱
Well, look, sam, I got no love for demons,
并且  是啊  整件事情都很疯狂
And, yeah, this whole thing is crazy,
但  我也不清楚
But...I don't know.
在一年的徒劳努力之后
After a year of chasing up zilch,
或许是时候发点小疯了
maybe it's time to go crazy.
是啊  或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
嘿  鲍比
Hey, Bobby?
怎么了
Yeah?
还记得你被附身那次吗
Remember that time you were possessed?
记忆犹新
Yeah. Rings a bell.
当梅格让你杀死迪恩时  你没下手
When Meg told you to kill Dean, you didn't.
你夺回了自己的身体
You took your body back.
只是来得及给我自己一刀  怎么了
Just long enough to shank myself, yeah.
嗯  你是怎么做到的
Well, how'd you do it?
我的意思是  你是怎么让自己意识清醒的
I mean, how'd you take back the wheel?
问这个干嘛  萨姆
Why are you asking, Sam?
如果我们能打开牢笼
Say we can open the cage.
很好  但然后又能如何
Great. But then what?
我们引诱路西法到牢笼前
W-we just lead the devil to the edge
然后让他自己跳进去吗
and get him to jump in?
你难倒我了
You got me.
如果你们引诱路西法到牢笼前
What if you guys lead the devil to the edge
然后我跳进去呢
And I jump in?
萨姆
Sam.
就好比
It'd be just like
当时你拿刀刺向自己
when you turned the knife around on yourself.
就一下  一下就好
One action -- just one leap.
-你们俩个傻瓜是不是想气死我啊  - 鲍比
- Are you idjits trying to kill me?! - Bobby
咱们刚刚才让你老哥悬崖勒马
We just got done talking your brother off the ledge,
现在又是你  排队等着说“同意”
and now you're lining up to say "Yes"?
不是你想的那样  只有你和迪恩都同意
It's not like that. I'm not gonna do it.
我才会那么做
Not unless we all agree.
我觉得这起码算是一个选择吧
But I think we got to look at our options.
这不在选择范围之内  萨姆
This isn't an option, Sam.
为何不呢
Why not?
你不能这么做
You can't do it.
那种夺回意识的成功率微乎其微
What I did was a million-to-one,
而且和我进行脑力搏击的恶魔
And that was some pissant demon
只是个小猫小狗的角色
I was brain-wrestling.
现在你说的是
You're talking about
要从路西法手中夺回自己的身体
taking back control from Satan himself.
是  是的  是这个意思
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
孩子
Kid...
叫它“附身”是有原因的
It's called "Possession" For a reason.
你应该最清楚不过了
You, of all people, ought to know.
我已足够强大了
I'm strong enough.
你还没有
You ain't.
他会找出你的所有弱点  萨姆
He's gonna find every chink in your armor, Sam,
然后用其对抗你
And use it against you --
你的恐惧  悲伤  愤怒
Your fear, your grief, your anger.
而且实话实说
And let's face it --
你对愤怒情绪的控制可并不怎么好
You're not exactly Mr. Anger management.
你都控制不了自己
How are you gonna control the devil
又怎么能控制路西法呢
When you can't control yourself?
恶魔吗
Demons?
不  只是些人类肉盾
Nah. Human shields.
那个恶魔在顶层  十二楼
The demons are up top -- 12th floor.
好吧
All right, then.
我们必须在楼后面找到一个入口
We'll have to find a way in through the back.
你们温家的人总是化简为难吗
You Winchesters make everything so complicated.
妈的
Ah, crap.
靠
Oh, crap.
我干  日
Crap! Crap!
门是开的
Door's open!
怎么了
What?
你杀了他们
You killed them?
时不我待
We're on a tight schedule.
快点
Come on.
现在你到傲娇起来了  拜托
Now you're squeamish? Please.
上吧  猛男
Go get 'em, tiger.
你不来吗
You're not coming?
不了  上面不安全  那些都是恶魔
Oh, no. It's not safe up there. There's demons.
嗯  我知道
Yeah, I get that.
听着  只要按我说的做
Look, just do what I told you,
施展你的说服力
A-and try to be convincing.
效果绝对意想不到  相信我
It'll work like a charm. Trust me.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean winchester.
怎么  没有预约吗
What, no appointment?
这可是垂死挣扎的关头
Kind of an 11th-hour thing, you know?
那你刚好准时
Well, then, you're just on time.
请坐
Have a seat.
你弟弟还好吗
How's your brother?
好吧  我们来说正事
Well, down to business, then.
我能为你做些什么
What can I do for you?
事实上刚好相反  是我能为你做什么
Actually, it's about what I can do for you.
是吗
Really?
我和萨姆干掉了你的两个伙计
Me and Sam dropped two of your jockeys.
我想你知道此事
I think you know that.
是的  我听说了
Yes. I got the memo.
我们拿了他们神秘且蕴含强大力量的戒指
Well, we kept their, uh, secret power rings.
这就是我来这儿的原因
Which is why I'm here.
我听说你想要回它们
I heard some folks saying that you wanted them back
哪怕会付出一些代价
And you were willing to pay.
嗯
Hmm.
它们在哪儿
Where are they?
不在这儿
Not here.
但如果你想要回它们  你就得跟我走
But you want them, you'll come with me --
不准动手动脚
Nice and civil --
我们先离开这座威廉古堡
We'll get out of your little batcave here,
而后  我们商讨一下这笔交易
And we'll discuss a transaction.
谁说我想要回那些戒指
Who says I want them?
啥
What?
谁说我想要回那些戒指
Who...Says... I want them?
这个嘛...
You know...
别人说的呀
folks.
这么说吧
See...
战争和饥荒
...war and famine,
即使我再把戒指给他们戴上
even if I could cram the rings back on their bony fingers,
这恐怕也起不了多大作用
I doubt it would do much good.
他们只剩干瘪的躯壳
They're withered husks right now --
像胎儿般蜷缩在地上
fetal position on the floor --
这都多亏了你啊
all thanks to you.
我根本不想要戒指
So I don't want the rings.
我只想报仇
What I want is retribution.
我现在就要给你点颜色看看
And I'm gonna rip it right out of your ass!
这简直
This...
太棒了
...is so good.
太痛快了
Therapeutic, for sure.
迪恩  你知道吗  我太感激你了
You know, Dean, I really owe you one, buddy,
因为我感觉
'cause I feel...
比以前
so...
好
much...
多了
better!
迪恩  你跑去哪里啦
Dean, where are you going?
别跑啊  我们才刚开始呢
Come on, we're just getting started!
迪恩  又碰面了哈
Good meeting, Dean.
我非常兴奋
You know, I'm excited.
大叔  晚上好
Evening, uncle.
到底怎么回事
What the hell was that?
这太完美了
That was perfect.
完美
Perfect?
他不想要戒指  他要我
He didn't want the rings. He wanted me.
料到了你会大吃一惊的
Imagine the surprise on your face.
什么
What?
你的无知和误报
Your ignorance and misinformation --
完全是真实的
I mean, completely authentic.
这个你不可能假装得出来
You can't fake that.
怎么啦  进展很顺利啊
What? I-it went like clockwork.
我可不觉得  你这个狗娘养的
Not for me, you son of a bitch!
可结果就这样  谁叫你和恶魔合作呢
That's what you get -- working with a demon.
嘿  帅哥  小心我的坐垫
Hey, hot stuff, watch the upholstery!
去你的  伙伴
Up yours, mate.
这些刻印能够把他困住
This bit of carving will tie our friend here down.
不用杀掉  不用驱散
No zapping off, no smoking out --
就把他困在肉身里
locked in the meat suit...
这有利于我们跟他讨价还价
An important piece of our bargaining strategy.
现在从这上去  我们不走I-50道
Now, up here, we don't want I-50.
我们去93号路 往北方向
Take 93 north.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我们不能带他到你弟弟那儿去
Look, we can't take this guy back to your brother.
为什么不能
Why the hell not?
克劳力
Crowley!
他们之前认识  好了吧
They got history, all right?
想走就先老实交代
You want to go anywhere, you start talking.
他们什么关系
What history?
迪恩在哪儿
Where's Dean?
现在
Now...
话说前头  我很反对这么做
for the record, I'm against this.
关于高层人士变节的协商
Negotiating a high-level defection --
是非常棘手的事情
it's very delicate business.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我求过迪恩不要回来
I begged Dean not to come back.
我们本来应该远离你的
We should be miles away... from you.
他却华丽丽地对我说
He replied with a colorful rejoinder
关我屁事
about my "Corn Chute."
那么  去吧
So, go ahead.
去吧  毁掉我们最后的希望
Go -- ruin our last best hope.
只是世界末日罢了
It's only the end of the world.
萨姆
Sam.
迪恩  怎么了
What's going on, Dean?
一切都听我的  好吗
I need you to stay on mission, okay?
认真点
Focused.
我不太明白  到底怎么了
I don't understand. What's all this about?
我这么做  是因为我信任你
I'm doing this 'cause I trust you.
信任我什么
Trust me to what?
萨姆
Sam?
萨姆  是你吗
Sam, is that you?
布雷迪
Brady?
我早就不是那个布雷迪了
Brady hasn't been Brady in years.
我想想  大概是从大二期中开始
Not since, oh... middle of our sophomore year?
-什么  - 没错
- What? - That's right.
那个时候起就有恶魔瞄上你了
You had a devil on your shoulder even back then.
好了  现在  真相大白了
All right, now, let it all sink in.
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
你这个狗娘养的  你介绍我和杰西认识
You son of a bitch! You introduced me to Jess!
对了  我想他明白了
Ding, ding! I think he's got it!
-萨姆  该死的  - 我要杀了你
- Damn it, Sam! - I'm gonna kill you!
够了
Hey, that's enough.
-让开  - 不
- Get out of my way! - No.
迪恩  让开
Get out of my way, Dean.
我们想赢的话  只有一条路走
There is only one way to win,
但杀了他没任何帮助
and it ain't by killing that thing in there.
很好
Well...
看来你们俩谈妥了
sounds like you got him nice and fluffed.
由衷感谢
Thanks so much.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们要瘟疫骑士的戒指来抓住路西法
We need pestilence to get at the devil,
而我们要通过布雷迪来找到瘟疫骑士
and we need Brady to get to pestilence.
为什么  因为是克劳力说的吗
Why? Because Crowley said so?
我们现在得相信他了吗
Because we trust him now?
就像我信任露比一样吗
Like I trusted Ruby?
或者像我曾经信任布雷迪那样吗
Or like I trusted Brady back at school?
听着  你自己算算这笔账
Look... do the math yourself.
如果路西法赢了
If Lucifer wins,
他会把这个地方变成他的天下
he'll turn this place into his kingdom.
覆巢之下
When the morningstar cleans house,
岂有完卵
we all get the mop.
他创造了我们
He created us.
干嘛又要消灭我们
Why would he destroy us?
这根本说不通嘛
That makes no sense.
这得看看
Look at who --
他究竟是什么
and what he is.
然后再看看我们又是什么
Then take a look at what we are.
也许你不用这么担心
Maybe you should be a little less worried
我们的小命
about our necks
多担心一下你自己吧
And be a little more worried about yours.
我想过  这不是重点
Has crossed my mind. That's not really the point.
克劳力  实际上这才是重点
Actually, crowley, that is the point.
没人比你更了解被折磨的痛苦了
No one will know greater torment than you.
路西法会永远折磨你
Lucifer is never gonna let you die.
至于我  我心里有数
As for me, I know the score.
无论是说或不说  我都死定了
I'm dead, whether I tell you anything or not.
所以我决定光荣献身  多谢
So I think I'll die on the winning side, thanks.
说得好
Good talk.
谢谢
Cheers.
怎么样  他接受你的建议没
Well, how'd it go? He buy your girl scout cookies?
还没有
Not yet.
你的麋鹿宝宝呢
Where's your moose?
他想冷静一下
He's cooling off.
那好吧
All right, then.
滚他娘的
Get bent.
你要出去
You going somewhere?
他不肯低头
Well, he won't budge,
所以我得出去探探风
So now I go stick my neck out.
你准备怎么做
What are you gonna do?
虚张声势
Exactly the kind of desperate swashbuckle
虽然我一向避免用这招
I've been trying to avoid.
现在我要去端了恶魔的窝
Now I go kick open a hive of demons.
这些戒指最好能起作用
This whole bloody ring business better work.
萨姆
Sam
别这样  萨姆
Come on, Sam
萨姆  开门
Sam,  open the door!
开门
Open the door!
终于来了
Well, here we go.
是不是要说遗言
We doing last words or no?
大二那年对吧
Sophomore year, huh?
布雷迪是个好孩子
Brady, here, he was a good kid --
正直坦率
Straight arrow.
真是你最好的朋友
I mean, your best friend, really.
完美的切入点
Perfect point of access.
那个感恩节
Thanksgiving.
正是
Yes, sir.
记得我放假回来那阵  放荡堕落
Remember when I came back from break all messed up --
从医学预科退学  吸毒嫖妓
Dropped out of pre-med, the drugs, the bitches?
那是新的布雷迪  就是我
That was the new brady. That was me.
还记得多少次
Remember how much time you spent
你试着劝我重回正轨
trying to get me back on the right track?
你真是个好朋友
You really were a good friend.
但黄眼恶魔送我回来不是为了交朋友
But ol' yellow eyes didn't send me back to be your friend.
我们知道你逐渐离我们远去
No, we could tell we were starting to lose you.
成了一个温文尔雅的
You were becoming a mild-mannered,
一文不值的窝囊废
worthless sack of piss.
得了吧  我们可不要那样的你
Now, come on. We couldn't have that.
你曾经可是我们的最爱
You were our favorite.
所以我用一个纯洁甜美的
So I hooked you up
无辜女孩来引你上钩
with a pure, sweet, innocent piece of tail.
然后我把她放到天花板上烤
And then I toasted her on the ceiling.
阿撒兹勒或许给了杰西卡致命一击
That's right -- Azazel might have put the hit out on Jessica,
但是  兄弟  是我享受了全过程
But, man, I got to have all the fun!
她也以为我们是朋友
You know, she thought we were friends, too.
就这么让我进门
Let me right in.
她正在烤饼干
She was baking cookies.
当我开始折磨她的时候
she was so surprised...
她是如此的惊讶和痛苦
so hurt when I started in on her.
来吧
Come on!
要是这样能让你舒服点  下手吧
Do it if it'll make you feel better!
下手吧  小萨姆  快点下手
Do it, Sammy! Do it! Come on!
来吧
Come on.
靠了
来了  等等
Hey, hey, hey! All right! Wait!
马上给你开门
I'm gonna open it.
-发生什么了  - 没什么
- What happened? - Nothing.
-我自己有眼  - 迪恩  我没事
- My ass. - Dean, I'm fine.
是吗  那布雷迪呢
Yeah? And what about Brady?
就像你说的
Like you said...
我们需要他
...We need him.
天哪  多艰苦的一天
God. The day I've had.
好消息
Good news.
你可以长命百岁了
You're going to live forever.
你干了什么
What did you do?
去了个恶魔的巢穴  小开了下杀戒
Went over to a demons' nest -- had a little massacre.
可惜技术有点退步
Must be losing my touch, though --
留了一个活口
Let one of the little toads live.
哎呀
Oops.
然后还不小心说漏了嘴
Also might have given said toad the impression
说你昨晚你离开岗位
That you left your post last night
因为你和我
Because you and I are --
好戏来了
Wait for it --
我们是反撒旦联盟中的一对爱人
Lovers in league against Satan.
你好哦  亲爱的
Hello, darling.
所以现在你不会死了
So, now death is off the table.
现在你上了老大的永世折磨者名单了
Now you get to be on the boss's eternal-torment list
和你亲爱的我一起
With little old me.
-不  不  不  不  不  - 不
- Oh, no, no, no, no. - No.
当然除了我们的炽热激情
Something else we have in common --
咱俩还有其他的共同之处
Apart from our torrid passion, of course --
就是胆小鬼的自我保护本能
Craven self-preservation.
那么  现在  告诉我瘟疫骑士在哪里吧
So, now, why don't you tell me where Pestilence is at?
天哪  克劳力
Oh, God, Growley.
那是地狱猎犬
Was that a hellhound?
恐怕是的
I'd say yeah.
怎么会有地狱猎犬
Why was that a hellhound?
那是什么
What's that?
还记得我告诉过你
Remember I was telling
我那个诡诈的跟踪装置
you about my crafty little tracking device?
是的
Yeah.
恶魔们在我身上放了一个
Demons planted one on me.
你是说地狱猎犬跟踪你到这里了
You're saying a hellhound followed you here?
严格来说  是跟踪这个
Well, technically, he followed this.
放我离开  我会说出你们想知道的所有事情
Get me out of here. I'll tell you anything you want.
-闭嘴  - 那我们快逃
- Shut up. - Okay, well, then we should go.
对不起  同学们  没人比我更了解地狱猎犬了
Sorry, boys. No one knows more about the hounds than I.
你们早错过逃跑的时间点了
You're long past the point of "Go."
-该死  - 我早说了
- Damn it. - I told you!
你可真本事呀
oh, well, good for you.
幸运的是  厨房里有盐
Luckily, we have salt in the kitchen.
我看着布雷迪
I'll watch Brady.
看着我
watch me?
把我从这该死的地方放出去
Get me the hell out of here!
小萨姆
Sammy!
盐
Salt?
该死  放我出去
Damn it, get me out of here!
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up!
好  真好
Great. Just great.
嘿
Hey!
你回来了
You're back?
算上我吧
I'm invested.
暂时如此
Currently.
安分点
Stay!
你能控制它们吗
You can control them?
那只不算
Not that one.
我带了自己的
I brought my own.
自家的比较狠
Mine's bigger.
好孩子  干掉它
Sic him, boy!
快走
Go, go, go.
快上车
Go, go.
我赌一千美金押我那只赢
I'll wager $1,000 my pup wins.
没错  瘟疫骑士肯定在那里
Yeah. I'm sure pestilence will be there.
谢谢
Thanks.
你怎么看
What do you think?
信得过
It's good.
你没理由撒谎吧
You got no reason to lie, have you?
我也说了  你我在同一条船上
Like I said before, you're in my boat now.
是你把我拉下水的  没的回头了
You've screwed me -- for eternity.
不
Nah.
没这么夸张
Won't last that long.
相信我
Trust me.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
为你好
I'm going to do you a favor.
到时再联系
I expect we'll be in touch.
这算什么
What is this?
天使和恶魔
All those angels, all those demons,
那些个狗杂种们
all those sons of bitches --
他们怎么就是不懂呢  小萨姆
they just don't get it, do they, Sammy?
迪恩  他们是不懂
No, they don't, Dean.
要知道  布雷迪
You see, Brady...
你应该害怕我们才对
we're the ones you should be afraid of.
我想你这回是来真的  伙计
I bet this is a real moment for you, big boy.
这会让你好过点吗
Gonna make you feel all better?
这只是开始
It's a start.
曾被我们牵着鼻子走  现在要弥补吗
Gonna make up for all the times that we yanked your chain --
黄眼恶魔  露比和我吧
Yellow eyes, Ruby, me?
不能全怪我们头上吧
But it wasn't all our fault, was it? No, no, no, no.
你自己选择相信我们
You're the one who trusted us.
让我们走进你的生活
You're the one who let us into your life,
任由我们一再地在你耳边低语
let us whisper in your ear over and over and over again.
有想过原因吗  小萨姆
Ever wonder why that is, Sammy?
为什么我们总能找到你的弱点
Ever wonder why we were so in your blind spot?
或许是因为我们流着相同的血液
Maybe it's because we got the same stuff in our veins
在你的内心深处  你知道我们是同类
and, deep down, you know you're just like us.
你之所以这么憎恨我们
Maybe you hate us so much because you hate what you see
其实是在憎恨你自己
every time you look in the mirror.
你就没想过吗
You ever think of that?!
你和我们恶魔唯一的区别
Maybe the only difference between you and a demon...
只不过是你生活在人间
is your hell is right here.
真有趣
Interesting theory.
查到了一些
Yeah, followed up.
全是凶兆
Nasty omens,
但都和死亡骑士无关
but none of it's death with a capital "D."
有什么事给我打电话就好
Well, just give me a ring if it turns into anything.
卢法斯
And, Rufus...
小心一点
you watch your ass out there.
别灰心  援兵来了
Chin up. Cavalry's arrived.
不错
Charming.
但那伤不了我
That won't work on me.
我叫克劳力
Name's Crowley.
可能你已经
Maybe you've...
你就是克劳力
You're Crowley?
这肉身
In the flesh --
是个在纽约还算成功的文稿代理人
of a moderately successful literary agent out of New York.
看来你听说过我
I see you have heard of me.
人家很喜欢这套西装的
I liked this suit.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
给自己找条出路咯
Looking out for Crowley.
什么意思
Meaning...?
温家兄弟在找第三只戒指
The boys are on to ring number 3,
但我们还差第四只
but we still need number 4.
我来助他们一臂之力
I'm here to help.
你知道死亡骑士在哪里
You know where death is?
不  毫无头绪
No. Haven't the foggiest.
那就给我滚出去
Well, then get the hell off my property
不然我用石盐炸了你
before I blast you so full of rock salt,
你这死娘娘腔
you crap margaritas.
别忙着举枪对付我
That's a mite unfriendly,
有这功夫闹脾气
seeing as I could be getting you death's location
我就能告诉你死亡骑士在哪儿
in about the time it'd take you to reload.
你是想从恶魔口中套出来吗
You're just gonna chat some demons up
他们可都认得你
and hope they don't recognize you?
当然不  那岂不是送死
God, no. That could get me killed.
但我知道一个小咒语
But there is this little spell that I know.
是吗
That so?
肯定有效
Results are 100% guaranteed.
那你还和我绕什么弯子
Okay. Then why are you snake-oiling me?
说起来有点尴尬
Well, it's a little bit...embarrassing.
有一个技术性问题
There's this... technicality.
要让这奇妙的事发生  有样东西必不可少
I need a little something to get the magic going.
什么东西
And what's that?
你许一个愿吧
You make a wish.
我可以满足你
I can give you anything you want, mate --
当然也包括死亡骑士的位置
up to and including death's coordinates.
我只是想要...
All I need is...
我的灵魂
My soul.
我可做过不少贡献呢
I've done more with less.
这么说吧  歌手们获得格莱美奖时
Let's just say when they're getting their Grammys,
功劳可不是上帝一个人的
they shouldn't all be thanking god.
鲍比  这交易很划算
It's worth it, Bobby.
考虑一下
Think.
好
Okay.
这是我的回答
Here's my counter.
真天杀的
Bloody hell!
脾气真大
Feisty.
滚开
Get out.
我马上就会还给你
I'll give it right back.
你以为我是傻子吗
You think I'm a natural-born idiot?
正好相反
Quite the contrary.
听着  你是该有所怀疑
Look, you're right to be suspicious.
但我是你的盟友
But I'm your ally.
我们有共同的敌人
Enemy of my enemy and all that.
我要把路西法封印回去
I need the devil back in his stock.
这其实关系到我的切身利益
In fact, my delicate ass depends on it.
我保证只是暂时借用
I promise you -- temporary loan.
我会马上还给你
I'll give it... Right...Back.